

About me

He mainly worked on the creation of adaptive Single Page applications, the development of various CRM systems, messengers, he was engaged in code optimization to speed up the work of sites and site redesign.

Contact Me

- +380 98 77 62 028
- rosokha.dev@gmail.com
- Uzhhorod

Nan Rosokha Front-end Developer

TECH SKILLS

- JavaScript (ES5, ES6+)
- HTML5, CSS3 (BEM)
- Sass(SCSS), Less
- React, Redux, TypeScript
- Webpack, Gulp
- Git, SVN
- Responsive and crossbrowser design implementing
- Photoshop, Figma



Education

- 2015-2019
 - Uzhhorod National University Specialist (in Applied Mathematics)
- 2019-2020
 Uzhhorod National University
 Operations Researcher
 Mathematician-analyst

Work Experience

- Front-end Developer
- | Freelance| 2018-2020
- Front-end Developer
- | Farvater.travel| 02.2020-07.2021
- Front-end Developer
- Redmonkey.tech | 02.2020-08.2022

Soft skills

Time management
Flexibility and ability to
manage priorities
Reliable
Motivated
Organized
Fast learner
Team player

Projects

Money24 Currency Exchanger+ CRM(admin panel)

https://money24.com.ua/ JavaScript (ES5, ES6+), HTML5, CSS3

Nodapes

https://nodapes.com/ JavaScript (ES5, ES6+), HTML5, CSS3

Farvater Travel (user cabinet, promotional pages)

https://farvater.travel/ JavaScript (ES5, ES6+), HTML5, CSS3, SVN

OSBB.work

https://osbb.work/ JavaScript (ES5, ES6+), HTML5, CSS3

Vinodex NFT Marketplace

https://vinodex.io/ React, TypeScript, CSS

NFT Marketplace

https://nftmonkey.online/ React, TypeScript, CSS

Private Messenger

https://cryptico.chat/ JavaScript (ES5, ES6+), HTML5, CSS3

Private projects

3 private projects with limited access
JavaScript (ES5, ES6+), HTML5,
CSS3, React, TypeScript

Todo application (pet-project)

https://todo-app-pet.vercel.app/ React, Redux, CSS